Contact

lindsaymuratore09@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lindsaymuratore (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Health
Clinical Nutrition
Organization

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Professional Working)

Certifications

First Aid and CPR/AED

Nursing Honor Society Member Upsilon Chapter

Emergency Neurological Life Support

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau Member International Nursing Honor Society

Lindsay Muratore, RN, BSN

Clinical Researcher at Dr. Fajgenbaum's COVID Response Team Greater New York City Area

Summary

Registered Nurse with a diverse background in healthcare currently specializing in neurology, neurosurgery and orthopedics at Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center. My varied background working in healthcare for the past 10 years has allowed me to become familiar with a multitude of different perspectives in the industry. Dog and animal-lover at heart and passionate about traveling to experience different cultures.

Please feel free to reach out via the LinkedIn Messenger or my email at lindsaymuratore09@gmail.com

Neurology, Neurosurgery, and Orthopedics Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center

Experience

Dr. Fajgenbaum's COVID Response Team Clinical Researcher May 2020 - Present (3 months)

Read through medical literature to extract drug repurposing for COVID-19. Working on a database

Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center Registered Nurse April 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) 1275 York Avenue, New York, NY

Virginia Mason Medical Center Patient Care Technician Oncology September 2016 - August 2017 (1 year) Seattle, WA Skyline Terrace Nursing Home Medical Technician and Nursing Assistant April 2016 - November 2016 (8 months) Seattle, WA

WIC

Public Health Nutritionist I May 2015 - January 2016 (9 months)

Burlington, Vermont Area

Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine Research Associate March 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 6 months)

Washington D.C. Metro Area

Responsibilities included nutrition-based data collection and analysis, literature reviews, assisting with and working at the 2014 Annual International Conference on Diabetes in Washington, DC, and completion of PCRM's 2014 Airport Travel Guide; A Dietician's Guide to Eating Healthfully on the Fly!

University of Vermont Tutor August 2012 - August 2015 (3 years 1 month) Learning Cooperative

The University of Vermont Medical Center 3 years 11 months

Research Associate
August 2011 - June 2015 (3 years 11 months)

Emergency Department

Screen and enroll emergency department patients for ongoing clinical research and quality improvement projects under the supervision of The University of Vermont Medical Center emergency physicians. All of the research projects are aimed at improving patient outcomes. Research associates participate daily in the innovation of emergency medical practice.

Food Service Worker August 2013 - February 2014 (7 months)

Preparing and delivering food for patients around the hospital

Trader Duke's Restaurant Server

August 2014 - May 2015 (10 months)

South Burlington, VT

Whole Health Nutrition, LLC Clinical Nutrition Intern August 2014 - May 2015 (10 months)

Nutrition-consulting group; Responsibilities included writing blog posts for their website regarding digestive and athletic health, analyzing 24-hr nutrition recalls and creating one week sample menus for patients based on various health problems.

Babies to Boomers VT Nanny and Elder Care Provider August 2012 - May 2015 (2 years 10 months) Vermont Area

WIC

WIC (Women, Infants, Children) Intern August 2012 - May 2014 (1 year 10 months) Burlington, VT

Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine Nutrition Intern 2009 - 2014 (5 years) Washignton, DC

My responsibilities include literature reviews, writing factsheets, preparing the Airport Food Review for 2014, helping to organize the International Conference on Diabetes, organization

Education

New York University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2017 - 2018)

University of Vermont
Bachelor's Degree, Dietetics · (2011 - 2015)